# **Lokesh Patidar**

# Full-Stack Developer

+91 9993977820

■ bansiyalokesh29988@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/lokesh-patidar

▶ Portfolio

github.com/lokesh-patidar

Nalkheda (Madhya Pradesh)

## **SUMMARY**

Highly motivated IT professional with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, MongoDB, Node.js, and Express.js. Known for strong work ethic, adaptability, and collaborative spirit. Demonstrated ability to excel in team environments while taking initiative to drive projects forward.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Full-Stack Web Development (full time)

Masai School (Coding School) May 2022 – Mar 2023 | Bengaluru, India

# 12th, M.P. Board of secondary Education, Bhopal

Kamla Sagar High School 2017 | Nalkheda, Madhya Pradesh

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML & CSS | JavaScript | Typescript
Git | Next.js | React.js | Node.js
Express.js | Mongo DB | Chakra UI
NPM | Redux / Redux Toolkit | JWT
Deployment | Tailwind CSS | Rest API
Postman | Sockets | Prisma

#### **SOFT SKILL**

Communication | Teamwork

# **LANGUAGES**

English | Hindi

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Full-Stack (MERN-Stack) Developer

Accpal

Feb 2024 - present

- Contributed to maintenance of Accpal, an accountant software, ensuring stability and reliability.
- Worked on both frontend and backend functionalities.
- Engaged in debugging and troubleshooting to promptly address issues.

#### **Frontend Developer**

Dashmed-web

Dec 2023 - Feb 2024 | Remote, India

- Implemented authentication features for Dashmed-web using Next.js.
- Enhanced user authentication flow and experience.

### **MERN-Stack Developer**

Webient Technologies

May 2023 - Nov 2023 | Gurgaon, Haryana

- Crafted robust admin panels for Pink Apron, Ub-Factory, and The St Lucian Hub-HubLA Admin Panel.
- Live streaming application with MERN-Stack.
- Executed significant web3 project with React.js for Bitgert.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### [1] Pink Apron Admin Panel

- Monitor and manage home chefs' profiles, including approvals, updates, and removals.
- Oversee menu listings and updates from home chefs, ensuring accuracy and quality.
- Handle order management, including tracking, status updates, and cancellations.
- Implement and enforce user policies, terms of service, and community guidelines.
- Generate reports and analytics on user activity, orders, and performance metrics.

#### [2] WebTaskit 🛮

- GitHub Link ☑
- Collaborated with a team of 5 members to develop a tasktracking website.
- Specialized in implementing robust task management functionality for efficient organization and planning.
- Integrated a calendar feature, enhancing user experience by facilitating event tracking and monthly scheduling.

#### [3] Pharmeasy 🛮

- GitHub Link 🛮
- Developed Pharmeasy, a consumer healthcare "super app" offering on-demand access to prescription and OTC pharmaceuticals.
- It is a demo project that I worked on with a team of 5 members, utilizing skills that I have learned.